ILR School Extension Division Records /3065
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division Records
1943-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3065
25 cubic feet
25 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists mainly of reports, conference materials, and educational materials.
3079047
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 13, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4063: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3062: ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3066: ILR School Alumni News /3069: ILR School School Scrapbook /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3079047
- Extension Conferences, 1946-1956. (Box 1)
  - Manpower Utilization Conference Binghamton, New York - Cancelled, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NYSSILR Labor Education Conference, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NYSSILR - Ralph N. Campbell, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Extension Teachers' Conference, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - United Steelworkers of America Labor Institute, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Extensions Teachers Conference, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Unions in Community Life, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - First Annual Professional Conference for Teachers of Industrial and Technical Courses, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Union Leaders - Soc. Sec. and Prot. Lab. Leg. - Tuesday (L. Gray), 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Extension Teachers Conference 6/5/48, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1956 Conferences (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Guide to American Directories for Compiling Mailing Lists, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Industrial Communication Council, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Conference on Personnel Problems in the Canning Industry, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Workers' Education Conference Feb. 9-11, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1st Short Course Feb. 5 - March 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2nd Short Course Account 5400 Apr. 1-27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Summer 1955 One Week Seminars (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1955 Seminar Information Elisa Becson + Misc. (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Extension Conferences, 1949-1956. (Box 2)
  - Summer 1955 - one Week Seminars (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Conference Leadership in Business and Industry Seminar, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Institute of Manpower Utilization Albany, New York, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Conferences of Union Educational Directors, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Persons Interested in Special Programs, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Inquiries SS '54, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 4th Annual Conference of Training Directors 5008/4, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Reports on Extension Teachers Conference June 24-25, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Educational Conf. for Fed. Labor Unions - July 24-29, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Institute for German Labor Leaders Feb. - 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Inquiries Re Summer Seminars SS '53, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations Cornell Industry, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Federal Labor Union Conference, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Conference for Federal Labor Unions, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Labor-Management Conference, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Labor-Management Conference, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Extension Conferences, 1949. (Box 3)
  - Institute for Administrators in Social Security and Related Fields, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mary Donion Lectureship, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Conference of Extension Teachers, June 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Workshop on Supervisory Training and Human Relations (Hospital Conf.), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Third Annual Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Training Directors' Conference, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Extension Conferences, 1950. (Box 4)
  - Research Conference March 17, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Extension Teachers Conferences May 19 and 20, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mary Donlon Lectureship, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - German Labor Expert Conferences (also German Signs), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fourth Annual Conference of Training Directors July 6-7, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Hospital Administrators July 10-14, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Labor Institute United Steelworkers CIO July 16-22, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Federal Labor Union Institute July 23 to 29, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Professional Conference for Teachers of Industrial and Technical Education August 14-16, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Housing and Multiple Dwelling August 28 and 29, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - University Personnel Policy Sept. 6-7, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Labor Marked Research 2/14-15/50, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Union Educational Functions 2/17/50, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Administrators in Social Security, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Hospital Administrators, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Development of Instructional Materials, National Security Resources Board etc., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Extension Conferences, 1951. (Box 5)
  - Industrial Education Conference July 10-12, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Council, Macy's 1-S Institute, Electric and Gas etc., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - New York Savings Bank Conference August 1,2 and 3, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Social Security Administrators September 24-28, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Social Security Administrators September 24-28, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Effective Utilization of Hospital Employees Oct. 24-26, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Training Specialists July 16-20, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Committee on Labor Education Dec. 12-13, 1951 Misc. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Employers Association Conference on Wage Surveys Dec. 7-8, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Machinists Conference, Steelworkers Conference, Macies Union S-1 Union, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews July 26-28, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Wage and Salary conference July 23-25, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Extension Teachers Conference May 11-12, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Training Directors Conference July 12-13, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Extension Conferences, 1951-1952. (Box 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, A.F.L. Local 3, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Conference of Extension Division Secretaries Ithaca and District Offices, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fifth Annual Conference of Extension Teachers Ithaca, N.Y. May 11-12, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - United Department Store Workers of America, CIO, Local 1-5, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Training Specialists July 16-20, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers of America Institute July 15-21, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Institute United Steelworkers of America July 15-21, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New York State Saviors Bank Institute 1951 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Savings Banks Association of the State of New York August 1-3, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - N.Y.S.C.C. - Trumansburg Conf., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews July 26-28, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Institute International Association of Machinists July 13-15, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Weekend Institute for the New York State Council of Machinists July 13-15, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - United Steelworkers of America-Conferences, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hospital Conference - Ithaca, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - N.Y. State Electric and Gas Institute, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Institute Savings Banks Assoc. of the State of N.Y., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Small Business Institute, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Social Security Conference, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Conference on Wage Surveys for Employer Associations, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - N.Y. State Citizens' Council, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Institute on Teamwork in Industry, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Institute for Training Specialists, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Feed Dealer Conference, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dunkirk Institute, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Sullivan County Bankers Association, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Sumerbank Executive Training Program, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Institute Society for the Advancement of Management, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hospitals Conferences, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - USA-CIO Conference 1952 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Extension Teacher's Conference, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Conference for federal Labor Unions, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - New York State Teachers of Economics, Social Studies and Industrial Relations, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Conference for the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers July 31- August 2, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Extension Conferences, 1952-1953. (Box 7)
  - Organization and Management of Personnel Management Workshop Seminar, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 6th Annual Conference of Training Director's Oct. 9-10, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 6th Annual Conference of Training Directors Oct. 9-10, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - The Western New York U.A.W. C.I.O. Summer Camp, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Seventh Annual Conference of Training Directors, Oct. 22-23, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Training Specialist - 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Union Wage Bargaining Problems, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - On-Campus Conferences Summer 1953 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Conference for Federal Labor Unions August 5-9, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Savings Banks Association of the State of New York, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Conference for United Auto Workers June 17-20, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Conference for the Development of Skills in Teaching in Local Union, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers July 19-25, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports of Extension Activities by Cities, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Steelworkers Conference, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Conference on Profit Sharing, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Savings Brooklyn, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Savings Bank Association, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Savings Bank Association, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Macy's S-1 Institute, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Fifth Annual Conference Training Directors, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - YMCA Conference, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - The United Steelworkers of America Conference July 12-18, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Extension Annual Reports, 1947-1948. (Box 8)
  - Photographs (1948) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Extension Annual Reports, 1947-1949. (Box 9)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Extension Division Annual Report, 1947-1948 Western District (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Extension Division Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Extension Division Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Extension Division Annual Report, Rochester, Syracuse, Utica, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ext Div. Annual Report, 1947-48 Ithaca District, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Extension Division NYSSILR Annual Report 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Extension District Reports, 1948-1953. (Box 10)
  - IULEC - Field Reports, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Western District Reports 1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Western District Reports 1949 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Western District Reports 1950 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Western District Reports 1952 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Capital District Reports 1948 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Capital District Reports 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Capital District Reports 1949 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Western District Reports 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Capital District Reports 1952 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Western District 1953 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Capital District Reports 1951 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan District Reports 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan District Reports 1950 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan District Reports 1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan District 1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Central District 1953 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Central District Reports 1951 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Metropolitan District Reports 1952 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Central District Reports 1949 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Capitals District 1953 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Capital District 1953 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan District Reports 1948 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Central District Reports 1950 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- N.Y.C. Office. (Box 11)
  - Cornell Calendar for Management Education and Organization Development, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Contract Negotiation in Private Industry Preparation and Practice, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Handbook of Union Administration Book 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Handbook of Union Administration (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Contract Negotiation in Private Industry Preparation and Practice, 1955-1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Contract Negotiation in Private Industry Preparation and Practice Basic Principles Course, 1965-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Contract Negotiation in Private Industry Preparation and Practice (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Contract Negotiation in Private Industry Preparation and Practice Basic Principles Course (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Advanced Role Playing (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Video Tape: A New Dimension in Training, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Collective Negotiations in the Public Sector (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - An Elementary Introduction to the History of the Labor Movement in America (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - An Elementary Introduction to the History of the Labor Movement in America (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Handbook of Union Administration Book 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Handbook of Union Administration Book 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - An Elementary Introduction to the History of the Labor Movement in America (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Handbook of Union Administration Book 2 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Handbook of Union Administration Book 2, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Misc., 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Dynamics of Union Organization A One-Day Workshop (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Dynamics of Union Organization A One-Day Workshop, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Dynamics of Union Organization A One-Day Workshop, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Role Playing: it's Application in Management Development (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Role Playing: it's Application in Management Development (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Role Playing: it's Application in Management Development (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Role Playing: it's Application in Management Development (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Acquisitions Unit NYSSILR, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Acquisitions Unit NYSSILR - R. Miller (Box 11, Folder 28)
- N.Y.C. Office. (Box 12)
  - Sewanhaka "Labor Relations", 1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Poughkeepsie, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Catholic Business Education Review, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Term Papers Clean Dec. 1958 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Summer Program, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Early History of Labor in The United States (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Herbert Livingstone Lorraine J. Sposato, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Case for Unions, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Stop Look Evaluate, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Labor-Management Relations Course, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Term Papers, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Final Term Paper, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Attitudes Towards Labor Unions - William Zahn, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Extension Division - Social Studies Program. (Box 13)
  - Social Status Report - 1950 (Hancock) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Term Papers, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Automation and the Worker - Robert J. Murphy (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Labor and Management in the United States, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - NYSSILR, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Source and Community Resource on Labor and Industrial Relations, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Labor Management Relations on the Local Level (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - H.S. Grad and Trade Unions - John Ferguson, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Corning Speeches - Panel Discussion, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Symposium State Education Department, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Grad Assistants, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Oct. 1, 1954 of Jamestown (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Board of Education Americanization Program, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Buffalo + State Teachers Soc. Studies of Buffalo Bd. Educ., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Fredonia, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - State University Units Oswego S.T.C. Harper, 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Memorandums, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Rowland, Robert, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Labor and the Government, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Completed Programs, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Completed Programs, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Service Courses, 1951-1954 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Completed Programs, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Completed Programs, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Completed Programs, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Betty Barton, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Manuscript (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Reed Richardson Material, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- American Airlines Program. (Box 14)
  - Human Relations in Administrators Seminar, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Organization Manual, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Introduction to Management - Orientation to Supervision Manual (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Business Management, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Chief-Foreman Survey, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Executive Organization, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - American Airlines, Inc. Operations Department, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - American Airlines, Inc. Revenue and Expense Analysis December 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - American Airlines Business Leadership Courses, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Human Relations in Administration, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Instructor Cards, A-C. (Box 15)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Instructor Cards, 1945-1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- C-E. (Box 16)
- F-G. (Box 17)
  - Instructor's Cards, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Instructor's Cards, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Instructor's Cards, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Instructor's Card, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Instructor's Card, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- H-K. (Box 18)
- K-Mc. (Box 19)
- M-0. (Box 20)
- P-S. (Box 21)
- S-U. (Box 22)
- V-Z. (Box 23)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Instructor's Card, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Extension Reports: The Buffalo-Niagara Area: Its Problems and Prospects; Handbook on Human Resources and Industrial and Labor Rel. in Albany, Ithaca; and Participative Management. Includes other miscellaneous labor relations pamphlets and newsletters. (Box 24)
  - Buffalo-Niagara Area (Boxed), 1955-1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - NYSSILR (Boxed), 1955-1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Extension Division Materials. Includes research project descriptions, minutes of faculty meetings, 1948-53, conference reports, job opportunities in N.Y.S. study.; manual of ext. div. (Box 25)
  - Manual of Policies and Procedures - NYSSILR Cornell University, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Carpenter - Project Employer Questionnaire, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Prof. Carpenter-Research, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Research Projects Faculty + Grad. Students, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - American Labor Movement, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Suggested Research Projects, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of Faculty Meetings 1948 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Memos - 1949 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Faculty Meetings 1950 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Minutes (ILR Faculty) - 1953 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Minutes of Faculty Meetings 1951 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Minutes (ILR Faculty) - 1954 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Union Conference on Research, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Management Research Conference 1948 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Management Research Conference- Dec. 9, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Government Research Conference- Mar. 3-4, '49, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Union Research Conference- Mar. 17, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Management Research Conference - Mar. 17, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Gov't. Research Conference - Mar. 17, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Charles Armstrong Manuscript (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Ditto Publication 1/29/48, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Labor-Management Outline, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Research Committee Meetings Minutes, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Research, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Course Outlines, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Directory of Unions in Up-state New York, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Job Opportunities Study, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Elmira Area, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Binghamton Area, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Rochester Area, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Syracuse Area, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - N.Y. State Labor-Management Committee (Misc.), 1948 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Elmira - Wage Study Project, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Social Security, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Lettersetc. to Book Publishers, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Research Projects in Process, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Staff Publications (Already Published), 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Research Materials, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Review -, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - ILR Review Complimentary Lists, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Research, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Buffalo Labor Market Reports Mar. 1944 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Studies - Labor Market Buffalo - M.F. Area, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Studies - Labor Market Buffalo - M.F. Area, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 43)